wordweb.info 2019-06-06

# WordWeb Software

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how WordWeb Software uses and protects any information that you give WordWeb Software when you use this website or the various apps.

WordWeb Software is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using our websites, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

WordWeb Software may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 2 April 2018.

### What we collect

In most apps, including Android, iOS and Windows Store apps, WordWeb Software collects no information about you during routine use of the apps. Your IP address may be available to external web sites that you view.

When using our websites, or obtaining apps from an app store, we may collect the following information where relevant:

  * name, job title and company 
  * contact information including email address 
  * demographic information such as country, language, operating system and postcode 
  * purchase and upgrade history, and other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, upgrades, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. Customers who purchase directly from our site (rather than via app stores) can change the email preferences on the [data options page](https://wordweb.info/data_options.html).
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We would only contact you by email. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. The file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, for example displaying most relevant for your country of residence.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used, e.g. Google Analytics. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to remember your locale and payment currency, as well as licensing information for existing customers. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website and apps may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. If you need a restricted dictionary app with no web access enabled see WordWeb Minimal.

### Controlling your personal information.

Desktop customers may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information using the [data options page](https://wordweb.info/data_options.html):

  * Customers can change email preferences for newsletters, upgrade and other announcements 
  * Customers can request deletion of their personally identifiable information (like email address), at the expense of no longer being able to use product upgrades or some other site features 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to our mailing address.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
